{
    "subject": "Michael_Bell__mayor_",
    "predicate": "livesIn",
    "object": "Toledo _Ohio",
    "human_readable": "Michael Bell, the mayor, lives in Toledo, Ohio.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.983953058719635,
            "question": "Is Michael Bell the mayor of Toledo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8909178376197815,
            "question": "Name the mayor of Toledo, Ohio."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8673525452613831,
            "question": "Where does the mayor of Toledo reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8559331297874451,
            "question": "Who is the mayor of Toledo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7714213728904724,
            "question": "What city is Michael Bell the mayor of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7508419752120972,
            "question": "What is Michael Bell's role in Toledo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7497111558914185,
            "question": "Toledo, Ohio has a mayor named what?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7283582091331482,
            "question": "Where does Michael Bell live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6850204467773438,
            "question": "In what state does Michael Bell live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2667176425457001,
            "question": "What is Michael Bell's profession?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Bell, the mayor, lives in Toledo, Ohio.",
            "html": "yago_19072_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what state does Michael Bell live?",
            "html": "yago_19072_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Michael Bell live?",
            "html": "yago_19072_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Toledo, Ohio has a mayor named what?",
            "html": "yago_19072_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19072_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19072_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19072_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19072_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19072_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19072_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19072_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19072_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19072_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19072_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention Michael P. Bell as a former Mayor of Toledo, Ohio, and one of the files even specifies that he currently lives in Toledo, Ohio."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Michael Bell, the mayor, lives in Toledo, Ohio.\" Specifically, multiple documents indicate his connection to Toledo, Ohio, including his role as Mayor of Toledo and his raised and educated background there."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}